<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on My Glasses Are Dirty 👓</title>
    <link>https://www.myglassesaredirty.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on My Glasses Are Dirty 👓</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.myglassesaredirty.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Technical Documentation Is the New Source Code</title>
      <link>https://www.myglassesaredirty.com/posts/docs-is-the-new-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.myglassesaredirty.com/posts/docs-is-the-new-code/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;How technical documentation has become a core asset — as central to the developer experience as the codebase itself.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In an age of Large Language Models and executable specifications, technical documentation is no longer a second-class citizen. It is the interface, the architecture, and increasingly, the source code itself.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This isn’t a metaphor. It’s a real shift — one that’s both technological and philosophical — and it describes the arc of my own career.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Api First vs Data First</title>
      <link>https://www.myglassesaredirty.com/posts/api-first-vs-data-first/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.myglassesaredirty.com/posts/api-first-vs-data-first/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Hidden Tension Between APIs and Data Models: A Case Study of Enumerations.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the world of modern system design, there’s a constant debate between API-first and data-first approaches. While each has merit, the real challenge comes from how these two worldviews intersect — or collide — during actual product evolution.&#xA;I recently encountered a perfect example that captures this tension: the humble &lt;code&gt;customer title&lt;/code&gt; field.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Journey Begins</title>
      <link>https://www.myglassesaredirty.com/posts/the-journey-begins/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.myglassesaredirty.com/posts/the-journey-begins/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Why I’m starting a professional blog in 2025&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, the journey begins&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In a world dominated by short-attention-span video reels, I still believe there’s a place for thoughtful, well-crafted writing on professional topics — as long as it stays short and relevant. I’m always generating ideas, making discoveries, and reflecting on my work, and it makes sense to share those learnings with the community. It’s also a valuable discipline to shape those thoughts into a coherent blog post.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
